https://www.bicronusa.com/privacy

Toroidal Power Transformers
Current Sensing Transformers (CT)
Advantages of Toroidal Power Transformers
Technical Guide for Current Sensing Transformers (CT)
Technical Guide for Shindengen Open Frame DC Solenoids
Technical Guide for Shindengen Permanent Magnet DC Solenoids
Bicron Electronics Website Privacy Policy
Bicron Electronics is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our web site and will not sell or provide any non-public personal information to anyone without your permission.
Terminology
Cookies. A Cookie is a randomly generated unique number placed on your computer. It allows the identification of your computer without requiring disclosure of any Non-Public Personal Information. Cookies make it possible to both store and retrieve information through your internet browser. A Cookie itself cannot read information stored on your computer’s hard drive or read Cookie files from other sites.
General Information is information that does not itself reveal your identity. General Information may include, without limitation: generic business type; SIC code; information derived from publicly available databases (such as Dun and Bradstreet); user behavior on our website; and aggregated generic information.
Non-Public Personal Information is any non-public information you provide to us or that is proprietary or identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate you or someone at your business. Non-Public Personal Information may include, without limitation: name; address; phone number; e-mail address; credit card number; technical details, and account information.
Information We Collect
Bicron Electronics collects general information and non-public personal information.
How We Collect Our Information
Bicron Electronics collects our general information through the use of cookies and server-based tracking systems to view the usage of our website.
Non-public personal information is provided by the users of our website and is collected through contact forms or technical worksheets available on this website. Non-public personal information will never be used for any purpose other than Bicron’s internal use.
Privacy Policy Changes
Any changes to this privacy policy will be posted here and unless otherwise noted on our website.
Changing Your Non-Public Personal Information
Please contact Bicron Electronics to change any non-public personal information provided to us through a contact form or technical worksheet.
If you have any questions or concerns about any privacy issues, please contact us.
Transformers
VoltBoss™ High Frequency Transformers
Partial Discharge & Corona
Toroidal Power Transformers
Current Sensing Transformers (CT)
Current Sensing Transformers (CT)
Bicron® Electronics Company | 427 Goshen Road, Torrington, CT 06790 USA
